A new ice age apocalypse.
Ice Storm is a science fiction, action, horror film directed by Jared Cohn.
When a devastating winter storm freezes over the whole of North Carolina, climatologists and
disaster relief experts are called in before the entire East Coast is destroyed.
Molly, played by McKenzie Westmore.
Eric, played by Grant Bowler.
Griffin, played by Tyler Christopher.
Senator Carlson, played by William Baldwin.
Chrissy, played by Tori Griffith.
Clay, played by Jessie B. Evans.
The Ice Storm is a 1997 American drama film directed by Ang Lee and written by
James Schamus adapting the 1994 novel The Ice Storm by Rick Moody.
During Thanksgiving in 1973, two neighboring suburban families seek escape from
their emotional emptiness through infidelity and self-indulgence.
The film stars Kevin Kline, Joan Allen, Tobey Maguire, Christina Ricci, Elijah Wood,
Katie Holmes, Glenn Fitzgerald, Jamey Sheridan, and Sigourney Weaver.
The film was produced by Fox Searchlight Pictures on a budget of $18 million.
The film premiered on May 12, 1997, at the 1997 Cannes Film Festival, where
Schamus won the Cannes Film Festival Award for Best Screenplay.
Fox Searchlight gave the film a limited theatrical release
in the United States on September 27, 1997.
It grossed $8 million in the U.S., and it grossed $8 million
outside the US for a worldwide total of $16 million.
Among other accolades, Weaver won the BAFTA Award for
Best Actress in a Supporting Role.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.